# Agustina Feijóo

UX/UI Designer based in Argentina, with +5 years of professional experience in screen design. Working remotely for the world.

Hi! I'm Agustina. Currently, I am a designer and partner at <u>The UX Department</u>, a digital agency with its HQ in SF.

I perform UX Research, interaction and visual design, and lead remote moderated usability testing sessions. I have participated in the creation and redesign of marketing websites, e-commerce websites, and both web and mobile applications.

uxagustina.com uxagustina@gmail.com +54 9 381 6 17 62 56 Skype: agustinafeijoodg Linkedin

## **Professional experience**

UX/UI Designer @ The UX Department

#### 2013 - Current - Remote

- I have worked with world-class clients, including: 4INFO, Oaktree Capital Management, IdeaScale and their clients (including several government agencies, universities and Fortune 500 companies), VSP Global, Rockwell Collins, Vibrant America, Constellation Brands, Black Box Wines, ATT Monitor, Control Arms, JRK Property Holdings, and more.
- I have participated and lead projects for financial, healthcare, advertising, real estate, social media, retail, and non-profit companies.
- I formulate the strategies and execute the design decisions to create platforms that support a client's business goals. I seek to create consistent design identities to strengthen the client's brand and to create a cohesive experience for the client's audience.
- Case studies: <u>Globespinning</u>, <u>Level</u>, <u>Vibrant America</u> and <u>Boostly</u>.

### Previous Experiences

- Graphic Designer for Maderplak in 2013.
- Freelance print designer in 2011-2013.
- Graphic Designer for TodoColor Photography Lab in 2010-2011.

### Formal education

- 2013 Bachelor's degree in Graphic Design, Universidad del Norte Santo Tomás de Aquino.
- 2017 User Research and Design course, University of Minnesota/Coursera.

### **Technical skills**

- **Strong:** Interaction Design, Visual Design, Information Architecture, Usability Testing.
- Knowledgeable: UX Research, Project Management, HTML/CSS.